Galuh Prahadi Gumelar

East Java, Indonesia | +6281358363661 | galuhprahadi04@gmail.com | github.com/gumelarid | linkedin.com/in/galuh-prahadi

SUMMARY

Graduated in Information Systems and also Bootcamp Pijar Camp. Having a web development experience for over 3 years with the Stacks I use include PHP, Laravel, Codeigniter, expressJS, VueJS, NuxtJS. Currently, I also study Data Engineering and IOT. I am a hard worker, a quick learner, and a lover of new things. I want to contribute to my country by doing something that will benefit society and I believe I can do it by being a great web developer.

EXPERIENCE

MNC Digital Entertainment (PT. Esport Star Indonesia)

Backend Developer Specialize And IT DevOps Support Publishing September 2022 - Present, Jakarta

- Analysis, developed, maintained, and tested code for app Payment, CMS, and Single Sign On (SSO), with Laravel, Nodejs.
- Integration with third party payment gateway to apps.
- Setup Server, maintenance and deploy App to Microsoft Azure and implemented new technology to improve game development and apps.
- Providing technical support to users via email or tickets for troubleshooting hardware and software issues.
- Assisting users in resolving everyday technical problems, such as issues with hardware, software, networks, or IT infrastructure.
- Monitoring system performance to detect performance issues or hardware or software failures, and taking necessary corrective actions.
- Creating and updating documentation on system configurations, maintenance procedures, and user guides to facilitate troubleshooting and knowledge transfer.

PT. Prima Mandiri Komunikasi

Full Stack Web Developer February 2021 - September 2021, Surabaya, East Java

- Developed, maintained, and tested code for in-house and client Web Apps.
- Participated in analysis, design, and development of the Prima Village application by serving as a backend developer using Laravel, completing the frontend and backend of the application ahead of schedule.
- Effectively communicate with clients to understand their needs, provide regular updates on project progress, and solicit feedback to ensure client satisfaction.
- Provide training to clients on how to use the applications or websites developed, and create clear and comprehensive documentation to facilitate understanding and usage of the product.

Sekretariat Daerah Kabupaten Trenggalek

Freelance Web Developer June 2019 - september 2019, Trenggalek, East Java

- Effectively communicate with clients to understand their needs, provide regular updates on project progress, and solicit feedback to ensure client satisfaction.
- Provide training to clients on how to use the applications or websites developed, and create clear and comprehensive documentation to facilitate understanding and usage of the product.
- Analyzed, designed, developed, and maintained applications management archive using PHP (Codeigniter Framework) to support performance.
- Administered systems and responsible for all operations, including installation, configuration, diagnosis, repair, and maintenance.

Sekretariat DPRD Kabupaten Trenggalek

Freelance Web Developer March 2019 - June 2019, Trenggalek, East Java

- Effectively communicate with clients to understand their needs, provide regular updates on project progress, and solicit feedback to ensure client satisfaction.
- Provide training to clients on how to use the applications or websites developed, and create clear and comprehensive documentation to facilitate understanding and usage of the product.
- Developed and maintained a company profile with wordpress and Codeigniter.
- Responsible for installation, configuration, diagnosis, repair, and maintenance.

Pusat Komputer Universitas Nusantara PGRI Kediri

System Engineer July 2017 - September 2017, Kediri, East Java

- Developed and maintained systems information, and network campus.
- Built desktop applications lab management Computer with Visual basic and Delphi.
- Administered systems and responsible for all operations, including installation, configuration, diagnosis, repair, and maintenance.

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree in information systems

Universitas Nusantara PGRI Kediri - 2018 - GPA 3.12

- Learned various programming languages such as C++, HTML, CSS, Mysql, PHP, Java. Built a management information system using PHP, Mysql, HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- Learned internet Networking, System Security, Mikrotik, Business Analyst, and Project Management.

COURSEWORK

Bootcamp Full Stack Web Developer

Pijar Camp - 2020

- Prepared for a career as a professional developer by learning programming that is most up to date with current industry developments. Earned skills are: REST API, Javascript, Node JS, Redis, MySQL, Vue JS, and Express JS.

CERTIFICATIONS

Belajar Dasar Visualisasi Data

Dicoding Indonesia – 2022

Prepared for a career as a data scientist by learning Data visualization using Google Sheets.

Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Belajar Dasar AWS Cloud)

Dicoding Indonesia - 2021

Prepared for a career as a professional developer by learning programming that is most up to date with current industry developments. Skill earned is AWS Cloud.

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Back-End untuk Pemula

Dicoding Indonesia – 2021

Prepared for a career as a professional Back-End developer by learning programming that is most up to date with current industry developments. Earned skills are: REST API, Javascript, AWS Cloud.

Full Stack Web Development

Arkademy Tech Academy – 2020

Prepared for a career as a professional developer by learning programming that is most up to date with current industry developments. Earned skills are: REST API, Javascript, Node JS, Redis, MySQL, Vue JS, and Express JS.

SKILLS

Programming Skills: Mysql, PostgreSql, PHP, Javascript, Laravel, Node JS, Express JS, VueJs, Nuxt JS, Codeigniter, Redis.

Technical Skills: Basic Networking, Design (Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator), Microsoft Office, Excell, and PowerPoint.

Languages : Conversational Proficient in Bahasa, English.